# VALENTINE KALCHEVSKI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER









#### **ABOUT ME**

Front-end developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, HTML, CSS, IS./TS.

My free time is dedicated to Codewars, programming tutorials and educational books. I'm expanding the horizon in back-end way. In the future I see myself as a Full Stack Developer.

I would like to find a project work/full-time job in a creative company with up-to-date tasks and collaborative team!

## CONTACTS

MY PORTFOLIO

CODEWARS PROFILE +375-25-732-18-33 valtikamore@gmail.com Minsk.Belarus

# LANGUAGES

English pre-intermediate (in progress)

# SKILLS

- React
- Redux
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Rest API
- Formik
- HTML 5
- CSS 3, CSS-modules
- Material UI, Ant-Design
- Unit-tests
- Storybook
- Git

### **EXPERIENCE**

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

Eehruary 2021 - Present

Creating apps using React and TypeScript, Redux state management and REST API.

Engaged in refactoring and bug fixing.

Cross-browser, adaptive, responsive development.

Migration from JavaScript to TypeScript.

Implemented flow-authorization, notification, forms (Formik and Redux-form).

Created Unit tests, Snapshot tests, component views in Storybook.

#### INDIVIDUAL ENTREPRENEUR

2016-2020

Superviced and trained employees

Conversation with suppliers and customers

Implementation of the sales plan, conducting price monitoring

# **EDUCATION**

### IT-INCUBATOR 2021

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT (REACT / REDUX / TYPESCRIPT

#### Colledge Business and law 2013-2016

ECOMINIC AND COMMERCIALIZATION

#### Other:

UDEMY, HTML-ACADEMY, YOUTUBE

BOOKS : GROKKING ALGORITHMS, HEAD FIRST: HTML

REACT